odditycentral.com 2014-05-27

# Privacy policy | Oddity Central - Collecting Oddities

## [Privacy policy](http://www.odditycentral.com/privacy-policy "Permanent Link to Privacy policy")

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for www.OddityCentral.com:

At www.OddityCentral.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.OddityCentral.com and how it is used.

We require all parties who wish to publish comments on our blog to provide us with their valid email address. We do not release your submitted email address to the public or any third party nor use it for marketing purposes. However, any information you publish via comments is made public, so please be careful about what personally identifiable information you publish on our blog.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.OddityCentral.com when you access our blog via web browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies, such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.OddityCentral.com  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. You may also choose to [opt out from online behavioral advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. Also, www.OddityCentral.com may use Google as a third party vendor. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.OddityCentral.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

www.OddityCentral.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

**Personal Information**  
Like most other websites, www.OddityCentral.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. www.OddityCentral.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Contacting our Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via email ( _Spooky2[at]odditycentral.com_ ) or through our [contact form](http://www.odditycentral.com/get-in-touch).
